Add it.
足して
I couldn't take it anymore.
もう我慢できなくなってきた
Can I just add it like this?
このまま足していい?
I'll add it.
足しちゃうよ
Just like that.
そのままそのまま
Push it up a little more.
もうちょっと押し上げて
Let's stick out our hands.
手突き出しちゃおう
Ah, back fat is coming out.
ああ、背脂出てきた
It hurts a little.
少し痛いな
Yeah.
うん
It would be better if it was erased more.
もっと消されたほうがいい
It's fun.
楽しいな
It's going to be fun.
楽しくなっちゃう
When you get off, it's fine.
降りたらあんまや
If you don't put the towel on top of it properly, it won't work.
タオルちゃんと上に置かないとダメだよ
I wish I could start over.
やり直したらいいな
Hand boots, hand boots.
手靴、手靴
No more suffocating when you're alive.
もう窒息させるときに生きている
You can take off the parts.
パーツ脱がしていいよ
Do you want to lick my dick?
チンコ舐めたい?
There was some weird fat on my back.
変な背脂出た
Can you see it when it moves?
動いたら見えんの?